Guide to the Abraham Hayward correspondence files: 1063 items, 1790-1889
The New York Public Library. Carl H. Pforzheimer Collection of Shelley and His Circle.
- Brougham and Vaux, Henry Brougham, Baron, 1778-1868, House of Lond - to Benson, Christopher, 1788-1868, 23 February 1831; HWD 05.024; letter (copy)
  regarding a petition and the University of London; also the Society for the Diffusion of Useful knowledge.
- Brougham and Vaux, Henry Brougham, Baron, 1778-1868, Brougham - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 September 1837; MISC 3507; autograph letter signed
- Brougham and Vaux, Henry Brougham, Baron, 1778-1868 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 July 1837; HWD 08.001; autograph letter signed
- Brougham and Vaux, Henry Brougham, Baron, 1778-1868 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.002; autograph note signed
- Bulwer, Edward Earle Gascoyne, Sir, 1829-1910, Naples - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 May 1872; HWD 06.004; autograph letter signed
  letter ripped in quarters, reassembled in plastic sleeve.
- Cadogan, F. W. (Frederick William), 1821-1904, 104 Picadilly - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 January [no year]; HWD 10.030; autograph letter signed
- Campbell, John Campbell, Baron, 1779-1861, Stratheden House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 January 1856; HWD 08.081; autograph letter signed
- Cardigan, Robert Brudenell, Earl of, 1760-1837 - to Winchilsea, George James Finch-Hatton, Earl of, 1815-1887, 17 June 1837; HWD 05.037; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, War Office (stationery) - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 November 1872; HWD 09.008; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, War Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 November 1871; HWD 09.050; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 November 1871; HWD 09.048; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 November 1860; HWD 08.052; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, "War Office" [stationery] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 November 1871; HWD 08.050; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.012; autograph letter (fragment)
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 October 1867; HWD 08.042; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 January 1859; HWD 08.045; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, War Office (stationery) - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 February 1872; HWD 09.010; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 January 1857; HWD 09.013; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, Ellerbeck Chorley - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 February 1859; HWD 05.072; autograph letter signed
  with envelope.
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 August 1867; HWD 02.046; autograph letter signed
  Carlisle v. II p. 160.
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 October 1860; HWD 09.014; autograph letter signed
  year from watermark.
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, Ribsden, Bagshot, Surrey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 December 1877; HWD 08.057; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 July 1864; HWD 08.054; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, Nightengale House - to [?], 26 August 9; HWD 08.056; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, War Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 October 1870; HWD 03.086; autograph letter signed
- Cardwell, Edward Cardwell, Viscount, 1813-1886, 74 Eaton Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 March 1865; HWD 09.011; autograph letter signed
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 February 1867; HWD 04.068; autograph letter signed
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 January 1858; HWD 04.037; autograph letter signed
  Signed Lady Evelyn Stanhope. She was married in Sep 1861.
  Signed Lady Evelyn Stanhope. She was married in September 1861.
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875, Highclere Castle - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 October [no year]; MISC 3509; autograph letter signed
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.094; autograph letter signed
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875, 66 Grosvenor Street W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 March [no year]; HWD 04.044; autograph letter signed
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875, Chevening Sevenoaks - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 May [no year]; HWD 06.052; autograph letter signed
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875, Highclere Castle - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 November [no year]; MISC 3510; autograph letter signed
- Carnarvon, Evelyn Stanhope Herbert, Countess of, 1834-1875, 66 Grosvenor Street W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 April [no year]; HWD 04.045; autograph letter signed
- Cary, Henry Francis, 1772-1844 - to [?], 21 July 1831; HWD 09.094; autograph letter signed
- Cavendish, 1831-1899, 22, Albion St, Hyde Park, W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 February 1873; HWD 07.032; autograph letter signed
  signed "Henry Jones"; begins, "I beg to thank you for 'Whist and Whis Players.
- Chambers, Robert, 1802-1871, Union Club St. Andrews - to [My dear Alenius], "Thursday"; [April 1866]; HWD 08.038; autograph letter signed
- Charlemont, James Molyneux Caulfeild, Sir, Earl of, 1820-1892, 14, Upper Grosvenor Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 February [no year]; HWD 05.078; autograph letter signed
- Chatterton, Georgiana, Lady, 1806-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 February "Saturday"; HWD 02.009; autograph letter signed
- Chatterton, Georgiana, Lady, 1806-1876, Hotel Wagram - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.007; autograph letter signed
- Chatterton, Georgiana, Lady, 1806-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 May [no year]; HWD 04.005; autograph letter signed
- Chatterton, Georgiana, Lady, 1806-1876, Hayle Place, Maidstone, Kent - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 February 1857; HWD 07.051; autograph letter signed
- Childe, E. V. (Edward Vernon), 1804-1861, Baltimore Md, 31 McCulloch St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 July 1838; HWD 10.056; autograph letter signed
- Chorley, Henry Fothergill, 1808-1872, 13 Eaton Place West - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 January 1861; HWD 05.066; autograph letter signed
- Chorley, Henry Fothergill, 1808-1872, 13 Eaton Place West - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 January 1856; HWD 09.019; autograph letter signed
- Christie, William Dougal, 1816-1874, 32 Dorset - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 January 1865; HWD 05.093; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 July 1865; HWD 08.059; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 November 1865; HWD 10.024; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 December 1866; HWD 10.023; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876, Bretton Park, Wakefield - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 July [no year]; HWD 10.020; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 June 1868; HWD 08.064; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 03.020; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 December 1858; HWD 08.055; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 November 1866; HWD 08.048; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 April 1869; HWD 08.053; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 November [no year]; HWD 10.022; autograph letter signed
- Clanricarde, Ulick John De-Burgh, Marquis of, 1802-1874 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 October 1867; HWD 08.049; autograph letter signed
- Clanwilliam, Richard Charles Francis Christian Meade, Earl of, 1795-1879, Isel Hall, Cockermouth - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.012; autograph letter signed
  Author could possibly be Richard James Meade, 4th Earl of Clanwilliam.
- Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 December 1860; HWD 05.085; autograph letter signed
- Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 February 1864; HWD 08.062; autograph letter signed
- Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 June 1859; HWD 08.047; autograph letter signed
- Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 April 1861; HWD 08.060; autograph letter signed
- Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 January 1862; HWD 08.061; autograph letter signed
- Clarendon, George William Frederick Villiers, Earl of, 1800-1870 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 May 1856; HWD 07.026; autograph letter signed
- Clay, James, 1804 or 5-1873, 25 Montagu Sq - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 February 1873; HWD 09.082; autograph letter signed
- Clyde, Colin Campbell, Baron, 1792-1863, Camp [?] Norwitch [sic] - to Canning, Charlotte, Countess Canning, 1817-1861, 11 January 1859; HWD 07.028; letter (copy)
  in an envelope addressed to Hayward.
- Cockburn, Alexander James Edmund, Sir, 1802-1880 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 December [w/m = 1870]; HWD 02.074; autograph letter signed
- Cockburn, Alexander James Edmund, Sir, 1802-1880 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, MISC 3520; autograph letter signed (fragment?)
- Cockburn, Alexander James Edmund, Sir, 1802-1880, 40 Hertford Street, May-Fair W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 November 1864; HWD 06.067; autograph letter signed
- Collier, John Payne, 1789-1883, 104 Eaton Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1868; HWD 02.070; autograph letter signed
  signed "J. Collier"; author identity not certain.
- Cook, John Douglas, 1808? -1868, G. 1. The Albany, Piccadilly W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 January 1867; HWD 06.024; autograph letter signed
- Cookesley, W. G. (William Gifford), 1802-1880, 11 St. Peter's Square, Hammersmith W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 March [no year]; HWD 06.092; autograph letter signed
- Cornwallis-West, Mary, 1858-1920, Rutkin Castle, North Wales - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 November 1882; HWD 02.041; autograph letter signed
- Cowley, Olivia Cecilia Fitzgerald, Countess, 1807- 1885, Dragrot House, Chippenham - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 March [no year]; HWD 03.030; autograph letter signed
- Croker, John Wilson, 1780-1857, West Molesey, Surrey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 February 1856; HWD 07.116; autograph letter signed
- Croker, John Wilson, 1780-1857, West Molesy, Surrey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 February 1856; HWD 10.071; autograph letter signed
- Croker, John Wilson, 1780-1857, West Molesy, Surrey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 February 1856; HWD 10.072; autograph letter signed
- Croker, John Wilson, 1780-1857, West Molesy, Surrey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 May 1856; HWD 10.074; autograph letter signed
- Croker, John Wilson, 1780-1857, West Molesey, Surrey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 February 1854; HWD 07.111; autograph letter signed
- Crowe, Eyre, 1824-1910, 33 Langham St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 July 1863; HWD 08.036; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 December [no year]; HWD 06.031; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, The Hoo, Welwyn - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 November 1867; HWD 05.041; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, 42 Ch. [Elyny?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 05.042; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.043; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.044; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 06.006; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Editor of The Standard, HWD 05.046; autograph letter (draft)
  on William Cobbett.
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 October [no year]; HWD 05.048; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 October 1855; HWD 05.040; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 05.050; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday, 3 o'clock"; HWD 05.045; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 06.032; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Cairo - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 April [1863?]; HWD 05.001; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Lord Warden Hotel, Dover - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 October 1867; HWD 05.051; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 February [no year]; HWD 05.052; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 March 1849; HWD 05.053; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 September 1862; HWD 09.068; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 October 1862; HWD 09.067; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Argyle Hall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 January 1868; HWD 05.069; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.049; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 08.006; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Rhoda on the Nile - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 February 1872; HWD 06.007; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 March 1869; HWD 05.004; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Constantinople - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 August 1862; HWD 05.003; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 February [no year]; HWD 05.047; autograph letter signed
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Constantinople - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 July 1863; HWD 08.005; letter (copy?)
- Dalling and Bulwer, Henry Lytton Bulwer, Baron, 1801-1872, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 April [no year]; HWD 05.039; autograph letter signed
- De La Warr, Charles Richard Sackville-West, Earl, 1815-1873, 18 Pall Mall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "25th"; HWD 05.094; autograph letter signed
- De La Warr, Charles Richard Sackville-West, Earl, 1815-1873, Shauncliffe, Sandgate - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.103; autograph letter signed
- De La Warr, Charles Richard Sackville-West, Earl, 1815-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 November 1869; HWD 01.074; autograph letter signed
- De La Warr, Charles Richard Sackville-West, Earl, 1815-1873, Shauncliffe, Sandgate - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 March 1857; HWD 05.002; autograph letter signed
- De Morgan, Augustus, 1806-1871, 91 Adelaide Road N. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 June 1867; HWD 07.078; autograph letter signed
  Among other things, asks: "Is there any record of Rogers having of feuded [sic] Byron? ".
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.001; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.056; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.041; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, [4 April?] [no year]; HWD 02.093; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 November [no year]; HWD 02.092; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.053; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.049; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.052; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.055; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 July [w/m = 1859]; HWD 02.084; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 June [no year]; HWD 02.090; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.051; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 March 1860; HWD 01.050; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 November [no year]; HWD 02.089; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.057; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 May [no year]; HWD 02.097; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Wednesday; HWD 02.098; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 March [no year]; HWD 02.099; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.058; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 November [no year]; HWD 02.100; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 December [no year]; HWD 02.096; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Sunday night; HWD 02.095; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.054; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Tuesday, 11th; HWD 02.091; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 December [no year]; HWD 02.085; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 April [no year]; HWD 02.094; autograph letter signed
- Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.048; autograph letter signed
- Denman, George, 1819-1896 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 07.037; autograph letter signed
- Denman, Thomas Denman, Baron, 1779-1854, Portland Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 December 1846; HWD 09.003; autograph letter signed
- Derby, Constance Villiers Stanley, Countess of, 1840-1922, 5, Portland Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.105; autograph letter signed
- Devonshire, William Cavendish, Duke of, 1808-1891 - to Benson, Christopher, 1788-1868, HWD 05.032; letter (copy)
- Dick, Quintin, 1777-1858, The Athenaeum - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 06.041; autograph letter signed
- D'Israeli, Isaac, 1766-1848, Athenaeum Club - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 January 1835; MISC 3495; letter signed
- Doherty, John, 1783-1850, Queen's Park, Brighton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 December 1847; HWD 06.062; autograph letter signed
- Donoughmore of Knocklofty, Thomasina Jocelyn Steele Hutchinson, Countess of, d. 1890 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.085; autograph letter signed
- Donoughmore of Knocklofty, Thomasina Jocelyn Steele Hutchinson, Countess of, d. 1890, 8 Chesterfield Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 March 1854; HWD 10.012; autograph letter signed
- Donoughmore of Knocklofty, Thomasina Jocelyn Steele Hutchinson, Countess of, d. 1890 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 November 1858; HWD 10.011
- Donoughmore of Knocklofty, Thomasina Jocelyn Steele Hutchinson, Countess of, d. 1890 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.013; autograph letter signed
- Donoughmore of Knocklofty, Thomasina Jocelyn Steele Hutchinson, Countess of, d. 1890 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.018; autograph letter signed
- Douglas, David, 1823-1916, 88 Princes Street, Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 February 1864; HWD 10.017; autograph letter signed
- Douglas, David, 1823-1916, 88 Princes Street, Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 November 1863; HWD 10.016; autograph letter signed
- Douglas, David, 1823-1916, 88 Princes Street, Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 April 1864; HWD 10.015; autograph letter signed
- Douglas, David, 1823-1916, 88 Princes Street, Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 March 1864; HWD 10.014; autograph letter signed
- Douglas, David, 1823-1916, 88 Princes Street, Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 January 1864; HWD 10.019; autograph letter signed
- Doyle, Francis Hastings, Sir, 1810-1888, Oxford & Cambridge Club - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.063; autograph letter signed